Alumni Memorabilia; Collection ua801.004
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Class of 1949, 1941-2014; 1949
  - Class of 1949 50th Reunion Program, 1999 June 04-1999 June 06 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 94)
  - Class of 1949 50th Reunion Songbook, 1999 June 04-1999 June 06 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 95)
  - Class of 1949 50th Reunion Photographs, 1999 June 04-1999 June 07 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 96)
  - Class of 1949 50th Reunion Dinner Photographs, 1999 June 05 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 97)
  - Class of 1949 50th Reunion Dinner Ticket, 1999 June 05 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 98)
  - Half Century Club Induction Certificate for Robert French, 1999 June 05 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 99)
  - Class of 1949 50th Reunion Dinner Photographs, 1999 June 07 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 100)
  - Class of 1949 50th Reunion Name Tag and Photographs of Bonnie Lewis Totten Adkins, Distinguished Alumni Award Winner at Reunion, 1999 June (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 101)
  - Class of 1949 50th Reunion Photographs of Classmates, 1999 June (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 102)
  - Gala Awards Dinner, Alumni Association Celebrating 150 Years Program (Photocopy), 1999 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 103)
  - Alumni Veterans, 2000; Undated (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 104)
  - Class of 1949 55th Reunion Program, 2004 June 04-2004 June 06 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 105)
  - Class of 1949 55th Reunion Yearbook, 2004 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 106)
  - Class of 1949 Reunion Questionnaire, 2004 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 107)
  - Class of 1949 60th Reunion Program, 2009 May 01-2009 May 03 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 108)
  - Tribute to Annette Gardiner DeLyser Read at 60th Reunion, 2009 May 02 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 109)
  - Class of 1949, 62nd Reunion Invitations and Programs, 2011 June 03-2011 June 05 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 110)
  - Memorial Service for Annette DeLyser, 2013 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 111)
  - Class of 1949, 65th Reunion Invitation, Program and Fact Sheet, 2014 September 19-2014 September 21 (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 112)
  - Advanced Dramatics, Joan of Arc Performance, Undated (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 113)
  - Cigarette Case, Undated (Oversized 6)
  - Class of 1949 Felt Banner, Undated (Oversized 6)
  - Chart of Existing Student Government-NYSCT, Undated (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 114)
  - Elementary Dramatics, Three One Act Plays, "A Husband for Mag," "The Happy Journey," and "The Feast of Ortelons" Program, Undated (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 115)
  - The Life and Death of MYSKANIA by Alfred Basch '31, Undated (Box 1 (1949-Class of 1949), Folder 116)
  - Poster Listing Names of Deceased Classmates of 1949, Undated (Flat-file 1)
- Class of 1950, 1946-2010; 1950
  - Photograph of Freshmen in Stokes Hall, women sitting around a sofa, includes Peg Howard and Jeanne Bowen, ca. 1946 (Box 1 (1950-Class of 1950), Folder 1)
  - Program for The Powdered Wig, presented by the Class of 1950, 1947 March 1 (Box 1 (1950-Class of 1950), Folder 2)
  - New York State College for Teachers Annual Catalog 1949-1950 (Box 1 (1950-Class of 1950), Folder 3)
  - New York State College for Teachers Directory 1949-1950 (Box 1 (1950-Class of 1950), Folder 4)
  - Schedule of Education class meetings in Richardson Hall, 1949-1950 (Box 1 (1950-Class of 1950), Folder 5)
  - The Sigma Lambdian, the official newsletter for the Sigma Lambda Sigma Fraternity, 1949 December (Box 1 (1950-Class of 1950), Folder 6)
  - Empty Purple and Gold "State College" Felt Scrapbook, ca. 1950 (Oversized 1, Item 2)
  - Invitation to Department of Librarianship's Spring Banquet, 1950 May 20 (Box 1 (1950-Class of 1950), Folder 7)
  - New York State College for Teachers Directory 1950-1951 (Box 1 (1950-Class of 1950), Folder 8)
  - New York State College for Teachers Directory 1951-1952 (Box 1 (1950-Class of 1950), Folder 9)
  - New York State College for Teachers Directory 1952-1953 (Box 1 (1950-Class of 1950), Folder 10)
  - New York State College for Teachers Directory 1953-1954 (Box 1 (1950-Class of 1950), Folder 11)
  - New York State College for Teachers Directory 1954-1955 (Box 1 (1950-Class of 1950), Folder 12)
  - New York State College for Teachers Directory 1955-1956 (Box 1 (1950-Class of 1950), Folder 13)
  - New York State College for Teachers Directory 1956-1957 (Box 1 (1950-Class of 1950), Folder 14)
  - New York State College for Teachers Directory 1957-1958 (Box 1 (1950-Class of 1950), Folder 15)
  - New York State College for Teachers Directory 1958-1959 (Box 1 (1950-Class of 1950), Folder 16)
  - Class of 1950 60th Anniversary Retrospective (alumni biographies), 2010 June (Box 1 (1950-Class of 1950), Folder 17)
  - Class of 1950 60th Anniversary Retrospective (alumni biographies), 2010 June (Box 1 (1950-Class of 1950), Folder 18)
  - Class of 1950 60th Anniversary Retrospective (alumni biographies), 2010 June (Box 1 (1950-Class of 1950), Folder 19)
- Class of 1954, 1935-2014; 1954
  Approximately 300 undergraduate students received their bachelor's degrees from President Evan R. Collins at the New York State College for Teachers on Sunday morning June 13, 1954 on the Alumni Quadrangle. Dr. Earl McGrath, president of the University of Kansas City, delivered the commencement address. In the days leading to commencement, the senior class participated in a class banquet at Jack's, a semi-formal Senior Ball at the Aurania Club, the Senior Skit and Torch Night.
  This series contains class directories, event programs, files related to Senior Week activities, newspapers, pennants and reunion materials. Of special interest is the Freshman Camp for Women brochure from 1950 and programs from the men's basketball team's games in 1950-1951 and 1954. As 1954 graduate Naoshi Koriyama is a published poet, there also are several of his publications in the collection.
  - The Memoirs of Edward Eldred Potter by Cordelia Rose Potter Lackey, 1935 (Box 1 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 1)
  - Freshman Camp for Women Brochure, 1950 September 15-1950 September 17 (Box 1 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 2)
  - "Call Me Freshman", 1950 October 28 (Box 1 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 3)
  - Class of 1954 Freshman Beanies, 1950 (Artifact-box 1)
  - Class of 1954 State College Handbook, 1950 (Box 1 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 4)
  - Class of 1954 and NYSCT Songs, ca. 1950; Undated (Box 1 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 5)
  - Jay Vee Cheers, ca. 1950 (Box 1 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 6)
  - Mini NYSCT Pennant, ca. 1950 (Box 1 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 7)
  - NYSCT Pennant, ca. 1950 (Oversized 1)
  - State College Pennant with Pedwin "Penguin" Logo, ca. 1950 (Oversized 1)
  - Primer, 1950-1951 (Box 1 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 8)
  - State College Directory, 1950-1951 (Box 1 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 9)
  - Jay Notes, Class of 1954 Newspaper, 1950-1951 (Box 1 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 10)
  - NYSCT Catalogs, 1950-1954 (Box 1 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 11)
  - Programs from Men's Basketball Games, 1950-1951; 1954 (Box 1 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 12)
  - Winterlude Program, 1951 December 08 (Box 1 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 13)
  - NYSCT Directory, 1951-1952 (Box 1 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 14)
  - Photographs, 1951-1954 (Box 1 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 15)
  - "Runaway Land" Program, 1952 March 01 (Box 1 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 16)
  - Soph Big Four, "Runaway Land" Ticket, 1952 March 01 (Box 1 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 17)
  - Brubacher House Violation Slips, 1952 March 21-1952 March 22 (Box 1 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 18)
  - "Stairway to Paradise" Program, Dance at Brubacher Hall, 1952 March 22 (Box 1 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 19)
  - State College News, Vol. XXXVII, No. 12, 1952 December 12 (Box 1 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 20)
  - Music Council Program for Platoff Don Cossack Chorus and Dancers, 1952 December 15 (Box 1 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 21)
  - Class of 1952 Graduation Book (Box 1 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 22)
  - Class of 1954 Upperclass Blue and White Felt Hats, ca. 1952 (Artifact-box 1)
  - Dramatics and Art Council program for Emlyn Williams as Charles Dickens, 1953 February 24 (Box 1 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 23)
  - Junior Prom, "Coronation Ball" Program, 1953 March 21 (Box 1 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 24)
  - Music Council Program for Jean Casadesus (pianist), 1953 March 27 (Box 1 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 25)
  - "April Showers" Program, Dance at Brubacher Hall, 1953 April 18 (Box 1 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 26)
  - Moving Up Day Felt Armband, ca. June 1953 (Box 1 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 27)
  - Winterlude Program, 1953 December 12 (Box 1 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 28)
  - State College News, 1953-1954 (Box 1 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 29)
  - Music Council Program for Robert Brink (violin) and Daniel Pinkham (harpsichord), 1954 March 12 (Box 1 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 30)
  - Newspaper Clipping from Albany Times Union, "Dance at Dawn New State Idea", 1954 March 28 (Box 1 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 31)
  - The Dublin Players Program for "Pygmalion" and "Shadow and Substance", 1954 April 05 (Box 1 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 32)
  - Moving Up Day Program, 1954 May 08 (Box 1 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 33)
  - First Annual Athletic Award Banquet, 1954 May 27 (Box 1 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 34)
  - Senior Week Order of Exercises Program, 1954 June 10-1954 June 13 (Box 1 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 35)
  - Senior Ball Program, 1954 June 11 (Box 1 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 36)
  - Torch Night Wooden Candle Holders, including On Candle, 1954 June 12 (Artifact-box 1)
  - Commencement Exercises Program, 1954 June 13 (Box 1 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 37)
  - Commencement Exercises Ticket, 1954 June 13 (Box 1 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 38)
  - Commencement Tassels, 1954 June 13 (Box 1 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 39)
  - Invitation to Commencement Exercises, 1954 June 13 (Box 1 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 40)
  - Primer, 1954 Spring (Box 1 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 41)
  - Music Council Program for Seymour Lipkin (pianist), 1954 October 15 (Box 1 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 42)
  - Class Card, 1954 (Box 1 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 43)
  - Class Ring (with stone missing), 1954 (Box 1 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 44)
  - Senior Handbook [for Senior Week], 1954 (Box 1 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 45)
  - Commencement Exercises Program, 1955 June 12 (Box 1 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 46)
  - Knickerbocker News Clipping on Moving Up Day, 1957 May 05 (Box 1 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 47)
  - Coral Reef by Naoshi Koriyama '54, 1957 (Box 1 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 48)
  - Mini Albany State Pennant, ca. 1960 (Box 1 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 49)
  - The Blue Jay Bugle, Class of 1954 Newsletter, 1972 (Box 1 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 50)
  - Alumni House Groundbreaking Ceremonies Brochure, 1974 May 18 (Box 1 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 51)
  - Alumni Day Brochure and Map, 1974 (Box 1 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 52)
  - By the Lakeshore and Other Poems by Naoshi Koriyama '54, 1977 (Box 1 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 53)
  - 25th Reunion Names Tags for George and Arline Lacy Wood, 1979 May 18-1979 May 20 (Box 1 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 54)
  - Alumni Weekend Program, 1979 May 18-1979 May 20 (Box 1 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 55)
  - Class of 1954 25th Reunion Directory, 1979 (Box 1 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 56)
  - Class of 1954 Reunion Photographs on Posterboard, 1989 (Flat-file 1)
  - Selected Poems: 1954-1985 by Naoshi Koriyama '54, 1989 (Box 1 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 57)
  - Poesie by Naoshi Koriyama '54, 1990 (Box 1 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 58)
  - Eternal Grandeur and Other Poems by Naoshi Koriyama '54, 1994 (Box 1 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 59)
  - Hawley Library Mural Bookmarks used at Class of 1954 40th Reunion, 1994 (Box 1 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 60)
  - Like Underground Water Translated by Naoshi Koriyama '54 and Edward Lueders, 1995 (Box 1 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 61)
  - Collected Poems by Naoshi Koriyama '54, 1996 (Box 1 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 62)
  - Class of 1954 45th Reunion Photo Album, 1999 June (Artifact-box 1)
  - Class of 1954 Directory, 1999 (Box 1 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 63)
  - A Collections of Poems and Translations by Naoshi Koriyama '54, 1999 (Box 1 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 64)
  - Beautiful Amani Island Folk Songs Edited and Translated by Naoshi Koriyama '54, 2001 (Box 1 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 65)
  - One Hundred Tanka by Naoshi Koriyama '54, 2000-2003 (Box 1 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 66)
  - Class of 1954 50th Reunion Directory, 2004 (Box 1 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 67-68)
  - Class of 1954 Memorial Placards, 2004 (Flat-file 2-4)
  - "Naoshi Koriyama's Anthology", 2006 (Box 1 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 69)
  - Class of 1954 57th Reunion Program, 2011 October 15 (Box 1 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 70)
  - Booklet of Poety by Naoshi Koriyama '54, Created for 2012 Excellence Awards, 2012 April (Box 1 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 71)
  - Class of 1954 60th Reunion Program, 2014 October 11 (Box 1 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 72)
  - 2004 Article by John Centra Discussing the New York State College for Teachers/Albany State, 2014 (Box 1 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 73)
  - Class of 1954 Roster of Fraternity Members, 2014 (Box 1 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 74)
  - Class of 1954 Roster of Sorority Members, 2014 (Box 1 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 75)
  - Copies of Class of 1954 Songs, 2014 (Box 2 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 1)
  - Beta Zeta Hat, Undated (Artifact-box 1)
  - Name Tags for George and Arline Lacy Wood with Blue Jays, Undated (Box 2 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 2)
  - Newspaper Clipping about Dr. Charles F. Stokes, Professor of Music, Undated (Box 2 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 3)
  - Postcards of New York State College for Teachers and Sayles Hall, Undated (Box 2 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 4)
  - Silver Bells on Blue Ribbon, Undated (Box 2 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 5)
  - State Fair Paper Corsage and Pennant, Undated (Box 2 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 6)
  - Who's Who, Ed. 20j with Seating Chart, Undated (Box 2 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 7)
  - State College Directory 1953-1954 (Box 2 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 8)
  - State College Directory 1954-1955 (Box 2 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 9)
  - Blue Class of 1954 hat with round brim, 1950-1954 (Box 3 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 1)
  - Blue Class of 1954 cap with small brim, 1950-1954 (Box 3 (1954-Class of 1954), Folder 2)
- Class of 1955, 1951-2005, Undated; 1955
  - "55" Armband, 1951 (Box 1 (1955-Class of 1955), Folder 1)
  - Freshman Handbook for the Class of 1955, 1951 (Box 1 (1955-Class of 1955), Folder 2)
  - New York State College for Teachers Annual Catalog 1951-1952 (Box 1 (1955-Class of 1955), Folder 3)
  - New York State College for Teachers Directory 1951-1952 (Box 1 (1955-Class of 1955), Folder 4)
  - Two Green Class of 1955 beanies, 1951 (Oversized 1, Item 1)
  - New York State College for Teachers Directory 1952-1953 (Box 1 (1955-Class of 1955), Folder 5)
  - Petagogue, 1952 (Box 2 (1955-Class of 1955), Folder 1)
  - New York State College for Teachers Directory 1953-1954 (Box 1 (1955-Class of 1955), Folder 6)
  - Petagogue, 1953 (Box 2 (1955-Class of 1955), Folder 2)
  - New York State College for Teachers Directory 1954-1955 (Box 1 (1955-Class of 1955), Folder 7)
  - Petagogue, 1954 (Box 2 (1955-Class of 1955), Folder 3)
  - Five Photographs of Commencement and Moving Up Day, 1955 (Box 1 (1955-Class of 1955), Folder 8)
  - Knickerbocker Press article on Professor Perry Westbrook titled, "SCT Professor Finds Murder Stimulating--Though Unprofitable", ca. 1955 (Box 1 (1955-Class of 1955), Folder 9)
  - New York State College for Teachers Directory 1955-1956 (Box 1 (1955-Class of 1955), Folder 10)
  - Petagogue, 1955 (Box 2 (1955-Class of 1955), Folder 4)
  - Four Photographs of Class of 1955 Reunions, 1965; 1990; 1995; 2000 (Box 1 (1955-Class of 1955), Folder 11)
  - Program and Directory for New York State College for Teachers Class of 1955 50th Reunion, 2005 June 4 (Box 1 (1955-Class of 1955), Folder 12)
  - Myskania Tassel, Undated (Oversized 1, Folder 2)
  - Rushing Regulations for Inter-Sorority Council, Undated (Box 1 (1955-Class of 1955), Folder 13)
- Class of 1956, 1955-2011; 1956; 2.80 cubic ft.
  Collection consists of donations from the Class of 1956, inlcuding reunion information, programs, pamphlets, graduation attire, and an obituary to a past student.
  - Note to Sorority Rushers, 1956 February 2 (Box 1 (1956-Class of 1956), Folder 1)
  - Cerificate for College Merchandise, 1956 (Box 1 (1956-Class of 1956), Folder 2)
  - Obituary of J.P. Wrinn, 1975 October 4 (Box 1 (1956-Class of 1956), Folder 3)
  - Program for Claudo Arrau Performance, 1956 (Box 1 (1956-Class of 1956), Folder 4)
  - NYSCT Directory, 1955 (Box 1 (1956-Class of 1956), Folder 5)
  - Notebook of James Partick Wrinn, 1964 September 17 (Box 1 (1956-Class of 1956), Folder 6)
  - 55th Reunion Announcement and Program, 2011 (Box 1 (1956-Class of 1956), Folder 7)
  - Pedagogue, 1956 (Box 1 (1956-Class of 1956), Folder 8)
  - 55th Reunion Invitations, 2011 (Box 1 (1956-Class of 1956), Folder 9)
  - Moving Up Day Ceremony, Undated (Box 1 (1956-Class of 1956), Folder 10)
  - News Ways in Numbers, 1969 (Box 2 (1956-Class of 1956), Folder 1)
  - News Ways in Numbers, 1969 (Box 2 (1956-Class of 1956), Folder 2)
  - News Ways in Numbers, 1969 (Box 2 (1956-Class of 1956), Folder 3)
  - News Ways in Numbers, 1969 (Box 2 (1956-Class of 1956), Folder 4)
  - Pedagogue, 1956 (Box 2 (1956-Class of 1956), Folder 5)
  - Graduation Cap, ca. 1956 (Box 3 (1956-Class of 1956), Folder 1)
  - Graduation Gown, ca. 1956 (Box 3 (1956-Class of 1956), Folder 2)
  - Psi Gamma Pin, ca. 1956 (Box 3 (1956-Class of 1956), Folder 3)
  - Class of 1956 Felt Banner, ca. 1956 (Box 4 (1956-Class of 1956), Folder 1)
  - Class of 1956 40th Reunion Collage, 1996 (Flat-file 1)
  - Class of 1956 55th Reunion Welcome Collage, 2011 (Flat-file 2)
- Class of 1959, 1955-1989; 1959
  More than 360 undergraduate students received their bachelor's degrees from President Evan R. Collins at the New York State College for Teachers on Sunday morning June 7, 1959 on the Alumni Quadrangle. The Honorable Earl W. Brydges, Senator, 54th District, New York State, delivered the commencement address.
  This series contains class directories, event programs, files related to Senior Week activities, newspapers and a 1959 sweater. The program for the first annual Parents' Day from March 16, 1957 is included.
  - NYSCT Directory, 1955-1959 (Box 1 (1959-Class of 1959), Folder 1)
  - Oversized Christmas Photograph in Brubacher Hall, 1955 December (Map-tube 1)
  - Sigma Lambda Sigma Annual Spring Weekend Program, 1956 May 04-1956 May 06 (Box 1 (1959-Class of 1959), Folder 2)
  - Moving Up Day Program, 1956 May 05 (Box 1 (1959-Class of 1959), Folder 3)
  - Program to "Play Ball," a Musical Performed for Moving Up Day, 1956 May 05 (Box 1 (1959-Class of 1959), Folder 4)
  - State College News, 1956-1959 (Box 1 (1959-Class of 1959), Folder 5)
  - Photocopies of Chi Sigma Theta Composite Photographs, 1956-1959 (Box 1 (1959-Class of 1959), Folder 6)
  - State College Revue "Plain and Fancy" Program, 1957 March 15-1957 March 16 (Box 1 (1959-Class of 1959), Folder 7)
  - Photocopies of State College News, Later Used for 40th Reunion Book, 1957 March 15-1957 May 03 (Box 1 (1959-Class of 1959), Folder 8)
  - First Annual Parents' Day Program, 1957 March 16 (Box 1 (1959-Class of 1959), Folder 9)
  - Junior Prom, "Journey to Avalon" Program, 1957 November 08 (Box 1 (1959-Class of 1959), Folder 10)
  - Junior Prom, "Magic Interlude" Program, 1958 October 18 (Box 1 (1959-Class of 1959), Folder 11)
  - Primer, 1958 (Box 1 (1959-Class of 1959), Folder 12)
  - Two Tickets to "New Girl in Town", 1959 March 14 (Box 1 (1959-Class of 1959), Folder 13)
  - Trinity Methodist Church Program, 1959 March 15 (Box 1 (1959-Class of 1959), Folder 14)
  - Moving Up Day Program, 1959 May 02 (Box 1 (1959-Class of 1959), Folder 15)
  - The Baccalaureate Service Program, 1959 June 07 (Box 1 (1959-Class of 1959), Folder 16)
  - Two Tickets to Commencement Exercises, 1959 June 07 (Box 1 (1959-Class of 1959), Folder 17)
  - Calendar of Events, Information for Candidates for Degrees, 1959 June (Box 1 (1959-Class of 1959), Folder 18)
  - Notes from a Speech Given at the Graduate Council Dinner, 1959 (Box 1 (1959-Class of 1959), Folder 19)
  - Pedagogue Yearbook, 1959 (Box 1 (1959-Class of 1959), Folder 20)
  - Senior Week Order of Exercises Program, 1960 June 01-1960 June 05 (Box 1 (1959-Class of 1959), Folder 21)
  - Class of 1959 30th Reunion Program, 1989 June 03 (Box 1 (1959-Class of 1959), Folder 22)
  - Class of 1959 55th Reunion Program and Invitation, 2014 October 10-2014 October 12 (Box 1 (1959-Class of 1959), Folder 23)
  - Copy of a Hand Drawn Map of Albany, Highlighting the New York State College for Teachers, Undated (Box 1 (1959-Class of 1959), Folder 24)
  - Green Sweater with White 1959 on Front, Undated (Oversized 1)
  - Guest List to an Open House at Brubacher Hall, Undated (Box 1 (1959-Class of 1959), Folder 25)
  - Information Booklet about the Hotel Wellington, Undated (Box 1 (1959-Class of 1959), Folder 26)
  - State College News Clipping "SCT Suspends Editor-Writer, Undated (Box 1 (1959-Class of 1959), Folder 27)
- Class of 1960, 1956-1985, Undated; 1960
  - Residential Life and Housing Letter to Freshman about moving into dormitories, "Important Information", 1956 September (Box 1 (1960-Class of 1960), Folder 1)
  - Phonograph Record - "Music for You" by the Saylesmen with the Neil Brown Trio, 45rpm, ca. 1956 (Box 1 (1960-Class of 1960), Folder 2)
  - State College News [5 issues], 1958 May 9-November 7 (Box 1 (1960-Class of 1960), Folder 3)
  - State College News, 1960 February 26 (Box 1 (1960-Class of 1960), Folder 4)
  - Telegram to Doris Hische from Bertha Brimmer, 1960 June 15 (Box 1 (1960-Class of 1960), Folder 5)
  - 1959-1960 Directory [2 copies] (Box 1 (1960-Class of 1960), Folder 6)
  - 1960 Class Beanie, ca. 1960 (Box 1 (1960-Class of 1960), Folder 7)
  - Photograph of State Education Building, ca. 1960 (Box 1 (1960-Class of 1960), Folder 8)
  - State University of New York College on Long Island Bulletin, 1959-1960 (Box 1 (1960-Class of 1960), Folder 9)
  - Yellow Ribbon and "Bee" nametag with name "Mary Ellen", 1960 (Box 1 (1960-Class of 1960), Folder 10)
  - Newspaper clipping: "State Marks 118 Year of Academic Growth: State Normal Opens Its Doors in 1844; College Eventually Acquires Campus Site," by A. Dugan -State College News, 1962 May 4 (Box 1 (1960-Class of 1960), Folder 11)
  - 25th Reunion Directory, 1985 (Box 1 (1960-Class of 1960), Folder 12)
  - Photograph of Reunion on Alumni Weekend, 1985 (Box 1 (1960-Class of 1960), Folder 13)
  - 40th Reunion Program & Class Directory and Invitation to brunch at the home of Bruce and Kristin Brossy Ginsey of Kinderhook, NY, 2000 June 11 (Box 1 (1960-Class of 1960), Folder 14)
  - Blazer with SUNY emblem, Undated (Oversized 1, Item 1)
  - College Song Sheet, Undated (Box 1 (1960-Class of 1960), Folder 15)
  - Chi Sigma Theta Sweatshirt, Undated (Oversized 2, Item 1)
- Class of 1964, 1960-2014; 1964